<AstroObjectEntry>
	<ID>DARK_BRAMBLE</ID>

	<Entry>
		<ID>DB_FELDSPAR</ID>
		<Name>Feldspar’s Camp</Name>
		<Curiosity>SUNKEN_MODULE</Curiosity>

		<RumorFact>
			<ID>DB_FELDSPAR_R1</ID>
			<SourceID>GD_BRAMBLE_ISLAND</SourceID>
			<RumorName>Feldspar</RumorName>
			<RumorNamePriority>1</RumorNamePriority>
			<Text>Feldspar headed off to Dark Bramble after reaching the core of Giant's Deep.</Text>
		</RumorFact>
		<RumorFact>
			<ID>DB_FELDSPAR_R2</ID>
			<RumorName>Inside the Seed</RumorName>
			<RumorNamePriority>0</RumorNamePriority>
			<SourceID>TH_IMPACT_CRATER</SourceID>
			<Text>When I launch my scout into the seed that crashed on Timber Hearth, it ends up in a much bigger space filled with fog and thorny vines.</Text>
		</RumorFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_FELDSPAR_X1</ID>
			<Text>Feldspar is alive! They crashed their ship and is now camping inside a huge anglerfish skeleton.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_FELDSPAR_X2</ID>
			<IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
			<Text>Feldspar doesn't think my scout tracker is wrong when it says my scout is in two places at once. They have a theory that space doesn’t work the same inside Dark Bramble.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_FELDSPAR_X3</ID>
			<IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
			<Text>Feldspar doesn't sound overly eager to return to civilization. They've been enjoying the (relative) peace and quiet.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
	</Entry>

	<Entry>
		<ID>DB_FROZEN_JELLYFISH</ID>
		<Name>Frozen Jellyfish</Name>
		<Curiosity>SUNKEN_MODULE</Curiosity>

		<RumorFact>
			<ID>DB_FROZEN_JELLYFISH_R1</ID>
			<SourceID>DB_FELDSPAR</SourceID>
			<RumorName>Hollow Vine</RumorName>
			<Text>Feldspar hinted that a secret to reaching the core of Giant's Deep lies at the end of the hollow vine they crashed their ship into. To find Feldspar's ship, I'll want to go to the tail end of the anglerfish skeleton and look for a flickering light in the fog.</Text>
		</RumorFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_FROZEN_JELLYFISH_X1</ID>
			<Text>Feldspar documented their attempts to eat this enormous jellyfish frozen in the ice. The outside was all rubbery and tough, possibly because it insulates the jellyfish’s insides from getting zapped by electricity.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_FROZEN_JELLYFISH_X2</ID>
			<Text>Feldspar decided to venture into the jellyfish’s interior cavity to see if it tasted any better on the inside.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_FROZEN_JELLYFISH_X3</ID>
			<ClueType>SUNKEN_MODULE</ClueType>
			<Text>After tasting the inside of the jellyfish, Feldspar concluded that these jellyfish are only useful for insulation from electricity.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
	</Entry>

	<Entry>
		<ID>DB_ESCAPE_POD</ID>
		<Name>Escape Pod 3</Name>
		<Curiosity>VESSEL</Curiosity>

		<RumorFact>
			<ID>DB_ESCAPE_POD_R1</ID>
			<SourceID>BH_MURAL_3</SourceID>
			<Text>One of the three Nomai escape pods never made it out of Dark Bramble.</Text>
		</RumorFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_ESCAPE_POD_X1</ID>
			<Text>One of three Nomai escape pods that crashed in our solar system.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_ESCAPE_POD_X2</ID>
			<Text>All three escape pods were launched from something called the Vessel, which was badly damaged.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_ESCAPE_POD_X3</ID>
			<Text>The survivors from Escape Pod 3 detected two distinct beacons from the Vessel, as if it was in two locations at once.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
	</Entry>

	<Entry>
		<ID>DB_NOMAI_GRAVE</ID>
		<Name>Nomai Grave</Name>
		<Curiosity>VESSEL</Curiosity>

		<RumorFact>
			<ID>DB_NOMAI_GRAVE_R1</ID>
			<SourceID>DB_ESCAPE_POD</SourceID>
			<RumorName>Escape Pod 3 Survivors</RumorName>
			<Text>The survivors from Escape Pod 3 abandoned the wreckage and attempted to return to the Vessel.</Text>
		</RumorFact>
		<RumorFact>
			<ID>DB_NOMAI_GRAVE_R2</ID>
			<SourceID>DB_ESCAPE_POD</SourceID>
			<RumorName>Escape Pod 3 Survivors</RumorName>
			<Text>The survivors decided to follow the closer of the two Vessel beacons due to their limited air supply. They planned to leave a trail of lights behind them in case someone heard their distress signal.</Text>
		</RumorFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_NOMAI_GRAVE_X1</ID>
			<ClueType>VESSEL</ClueType>
			<Text>The survivors from Escape Pod 3 followed one of the two Vessel beacons to a small Dark Bramble seed, where they could go no further.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_NOMAI_GRAVE_X2</ID>
			<ClueType>VESSEL</ClueType>
			<Text>The Nomai could faintly hear the Vessel's beacon from within the seed, but the opening was too small for a single Nomai to fit through, much less an escape pod.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_NOMAI_GRAVE_X3</ID>
			<ClueType>VESSEL</ClueType>
			<Text>The Vessel's beacon was dying, and would soon be gone completely.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_NOMAI_GRAVE_X4</ID>
			<ClueType>VESSEL</ClueType>
			<Text>If I launch my scout into the seed, I can take photos of an enormous derelict Nomai ship.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
	</Entry>

	<Entry>
		<ID>DB_VESSEL</ID>
		<Name>The Vessel</Name>
		<Curiosity>VESSEL</Curiosity>
		<IsCuriosity/>

		<RumorFact>
			<ID>DB_VESSEL_R1</ID>
			<Text>The Nomai warped to this solar system in a spaceship called the Vessel. They were attempting to follow a signal from the Eye of the universe.</Text>
		</RumorFact>
		<RumorFact>
			<ID>DB_VESSEL_R2</ID>
			<SourceID>BH_MURAL_3</SourceID>
			<Text>The Vessel crashed somewhere in Dark Bramble.</Text>
		</RumorFact>
		<RumorFact>
			<ID>DB_VESSEL_R3</ID>
			<SourceID>BH_HANGING_CITY</SourceID>
			<Text>The Vessel's warp core broke when the ship crashed in Dark Bramble.</Text>
		</RumorFact>
		<RumorFact>
			<ID>DB_VESSEL_R4</ID>
			<SourceID>DB_NOMAI_GRAVE</SourceID>
			<Text>I launched my scout into the seed at the Nomai Grave and took photos of an enormous derelict Nomai ship.</Text>
		</RumorFact>
		
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_VESSEL_X1</ID>
			<Text>I found the derelict Nomai Vessel deep within Dark Bramble.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_VESSEL_X2</ID>
			<Text>The Vessel's warp core is long dead.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_VESSEL_X3</ID>
			<Text>I activated a three-sided pillar on the Vessel's bridge that appears to be some sort of input device.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_VESSEL_X4</ID>
			<Text>The Nomai tried to call for help, but the Vessel's outgoing message system broke during the crash.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>DB_VESSEL_X5</ID>
			<Text>The Vessel can still hear incoming messages from other Nomai vessels. The remaining Nomai clans are regrouping in response to the impending death of the universe.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
			<ID>DB_VESSEL_X6</ID>
			<Text>I found a recording of the original signal the Nomai encountered from the Eye of the universe. The Nomai were worried the signal might disappear, so they warped before they could tell another clan where they were going.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
	</Entry>
</AstroObjectEntry>