<AstroObjectEntry>
	<ID>QUANTUM_MOON</ID>

	<Entry>
		<ID>QUANTUM_MOON</ID>
		<Name>Quantum Moon</Name>
		<Curiosity>QUANTUM_MOON</Curiosity>
		<IsCuriosity/>

		<RumorFact>
			<ID>QUANTUM_MOON_R1</ID>
			<SourceID>BH_WARP_RECEIVER</SourceID>
			<Text>The Nomai on Brittle Hollow observed a phantom moon that would sometimes appear in the sky.</Text>
		</RumorFact>
		<RumorFact>
			<ID>QUANTUM_MOON_R2</ID>
			<SourceID>CT_QUANTUM_MOON_LOCATOR</SourceID>
			<Text>The Nomai on Ember Twin observed a moon that would disappear when no one was watching.</Text>
		</RumorFact>
		<RumorFact>
			<ID>QUANTUM_MOON_R3</ID>
			<Text>A Nomai named Solanum landed a shuttle on the Quantum Moon.</Text>
		</RumorFact>
		<RumorFact>
			<ID>QUANTUM_MOON_R4</ID>
			<Text>Chert’s research notes mention a Quantum Moon that no Hearthian has been able to land on.</Text>
		</RumorFact>

		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>QUANTUM_MOON_X1</ID>
			<Text>I was able to land on the surface of the Quantum Moon.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>
		<ExploreFact>
			<ID>QUANTUM_MOON_X2</ID>
			<IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
			<Text>I found a dead Nomai in a space suit near the south pole.</Text>
		</ExploreFact>

		<Entry>
			<ID>QM_SHUTTLE</ID>
			<Name>Solanum's Shuttle</Name>
			<AltPhotoCondition>QUANTUM_MOON_X1</AltPhotoCondition>
			<Curiosity>QUANTUM_MOON</Curiosity>

			<ExploreFact>
				<ID>QM_SHUTTLE_X1</ID>
				<Text>A Nomai named Solanum landed her shuttle at the Quantum Moon's south pole and prepared to make the rest of the journey on foot.</Text>
			</ExploreFact>
			<ExploreFact>
				<ID>QM_SHUTTLE_X2</ID>
				<Text>Visitors to the Quantum Moon always arrive at the south pole (for reasons unknown to the Nomai).</Text>
			</ExploreFact>
		</Entry>

		<Entry>
			<ID>QM_SHRINE</ID>
			<Name>Quantum Shrine</Name>
			<Curiosity>QUANTUM_MOON</Curiosity>

			<RumorFact>
				<ID>QM_SHRINE_R1</ID>
				<SourceID>BH_QUANTUM_RESEARCH_TOWER</SourceID>
				<Text>The Nomai built a shrine on the Quantum Moon to aid in the pilgrimage to its sixth location.</Text>
			</RumorFact>
			<ExploreFact>
				<ID>QM_SHRINE_X1</ID>
				<Text>A Nomai shrine that wanders about the Quantum Moon.</Text>
			</ExploreFact>
			<ExploreFact>
				<ID>QM_SHRINE_X2</ID>
				<IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
				<Text>"You have recalled the rule of quantum imaging" is inscribed next to a mural of a tower on an island.</Text>
			</ExploreFact>
			<ExploreFact>
				<ID>QM_SHRINE_X3</ID>
				<IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
				<Text>"Recall the rule of quantum entanglement" is inscribed next to a mural of a quantum shard in a cave.</Text>
			</ExploreFact>
			<ExploreFact>
				<ID>QM_SHRINE_X4</ID>
				<IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
				<Text>"Recall the rule of the sixth location" is inscribed next to a mural of a tower hanging above a black hole.</Text>
			</ExploreFact>
		</Entry>

		<Entry>
			<ID>QM_SIXTH_LOCATION</ID>
			<Name>Sixth Location</Name>
			<Curiosity>QUANTUM_MOON</Curiosity>

			<RumorFact>
				<ID>QM_SIXTH_LOCATION_R1</ID>
				<SourceID>CT_QUANTUM_MOON_LOCATOR</SourceID>
				<Text>The Quantum Moon sometimes disappears, possibly to an unknown sixth location.</Text>
			</RumorFact>
			<RumorFact>
				<ID>QM_SIXTH_LOCATION_R2</ID>
				<SourceID>BH_QUANTUM_RESEARCH_TOWER</SourceID>
				<Text>Many Nomai went on a pilgrimage during which the Quantum Moon carried them to its sixth and most secret location.</Text>
			</RumorFact>
			<RumorFact>
				<ID>QM_SIXTH_LOCATION_R3</ID>
				<SourceID>BH_QUANTUM_RESEARCH_TOWER</SourceID>
				<Text>To explore the sixth location, the shrine on the Quantum Moon must be on the moon’s north pole.</Text>
			</RumorFact>

			<ExploreFact>
				<ID>QM_SIXTH_LOCATION_X1</ID>
				<Text>I met a living Nomai named Solanum at the south pole!</Text>
			</ExploreFact>
			<ExploreFact>
				<ID>QM_SIXTH_LOCATION_X3</ID>
				<IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
				<Text>The Quantum Moon is the Eye of the universe's moon.</Text>
			</ExploreFact>
			<ExploreFact>
				<ID>QM_SIXTH_LOCATION_X5</ID>
				<IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
				<Text>At this location, the Quantum Moon becomes a reflection of the Eye itself.</Text>
			</ExploreFact>
			<ExploreFact>
				<ID>QM_SIXTH_LOCATION_X4</ID>
				<IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
				<Text>The Eye is likely the source of all macroscopic quantum phenomena in the solar system.</Text>
			</ExploreFact>
			<ExploreFact>
				<ID>QM_SIXTH_LOCATION_X2</ID>
				<Text>Solanum wonders what would happen if a conscious observer were to enter the Eye.</Text>
			</ExploreFact>
			<ExploreFact>
				<ID>QM_SIXTH_LOCATION_X6</ID>
				<IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
				<Text>Solanum has a hypothesis that she may not be entirely alive.</Text>
			</ExploreFact>
		</Entry>
	</Entry>
</AstroObjectEntry>