<!--
1 - 3 - 4 - 5 - 6 - 7
|               |
2               8
Not Final
-->

<NomaiObject>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			CLARY: Here’s our first delivery, Yarrow: one warp core, fresh from the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Black Hole Forge</color>]]>! Root is installing this core’s sibling on <![CDATA[<color=lightblue>Brittle Hollow</color>]]> as I write this.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			CLARY: I wish I could wait here for you to arrive, but the forge (and my unfinished work there) is calling. I’ll return with more materials soon.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			YARROW: My gratitude, Clary! With this, the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]> is underway!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>
			YARROW: I confess, I’m deeply curious about what you and Poke found on the <![CDATA[<color=orange>White Hole Station</color>]]> that started this project. Could I visit sometime to learn more?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			CLARY: I recommend you do! The <![CDATA[<color=orange>White Hole Station</color>]]> is the model for the towers being built for the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Ash Twin Project</color>]]>, so a visit to the station would be doubly useful.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			YARROW: I suppose, more precisely, I would like to visit the <![CDATA[<color=orange>White Hole Station</color>]]> with <![CDATA[<i>you</i>]]>, Clary.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
			CLARY: I’d be happy to explain our findings!
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
		<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
			POKE: Yarrow, stop using this scroll wall to flirt with my sister (in romantic matters, her density rivals a neutron star’s) and go meet her on the <![CDATA[<color=orange>White Hole Station</color>]]>.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>WHS_R4</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>BH_BLACK_HOLE_FORGE_R4</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>TT_WARP_TOWERS_X1</FactID>
			<Condition></Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>TT_WARP_TOWERS_X2</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>