<!--
1 — 2 — 3
|
4 — 5 — 6 — 7
-->
<NomaiObject>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>
			COLEUS: How curious! This rock took me with it to a new location. I wonder why this happened?
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			COLEUS: Curious, but also alarming: This new cave appears to lack an entrance or exit. Also, the rock that brought me here disappeared while I wasn’t watching.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>
			COLEUS: The wandering rock has returned! Never before have I been so delighted to see a sedimentary specimen.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>
			COLEUS: I wonder if I myself became quantum briefly when the rock carried me here! This seems the clearest explanation. Hypothesis: If the rock can bring me here, it can also carry me out.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>
			COLEUS: My hypothesis was correct! I can travel on this rock, as long as I’m not observing my surroundings (meaning I must be in complete darkness). I’m going to bring my mentor here to see this.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>
			COLEUS: Melorae is here now, too. We theorize when a conscious being is in contact with a quantum object and ceases to observe his or her surroundings, the being can become entangled with that quantum object, and they move together.
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>
			MELORAE: Friends, Coleus has discovered a new quantum rule! (He has also promised me he’ll never vanish again, even if he <![CDATA[<i>does</i>]]> learn something useful from it!)
		</Text>
	</TextBlock>

	<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>CT_LAKEBED_CAVERN_X2</FactID>
			<Condition>5</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>CT_LAKEBED_CAVERN_X3</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>